(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],{16:function(e,t,n){e.exports={SideDrawer:"SideDrawer_SideDrawer__3Oaug",permanent:"SideDrawer_permanent__1gMC4",open:"SideDrawer_open__1FZ6w",close:"SideDrawer_close__2QzPz",navLink:"SideDrawer_navLink__1r4sF",home:"SideDrawer_home__1ud_f",appear:"SideDrawer_appear__2sdQk"}},19:function(e,t,n){e.exports={Container:"Home_Container__21aYr",Body:"Home_Body__1AT-5",body:"Home_body__1itaJ",base:"Home_base__3bnfJ",tests:"Home_tests__1C9Z-",logo:"Home_logo__2-RXw"}},2:function(e,t,n){e.exports={circle:"Option_circle__1zgqD",option:"Option_option__3OfOt",inner:"Option_inner__359Ex",incInner:"Option_incInner__1M0qa",slim:"Option_slim__2ttIS",container:"Option_container__2M6KW",containerSnippet:"Option_containerSnippet__1TxAH",selected:"Option_selected__lO9PC",inlineBlock:"Option_inlineBlock__2T0S_",false:"Option_false__3H8tU",true:"Option_true__3tScM"}},20:function(e,t,n){e.exports={question:"Question_question__1k2_y",options:"Question_options__2_mWs",container:"Question_container__3zG7R",option:"Question_option__omjvf",cover:"Question_cover__26TVz",rightSide:"Question_rightSide__3s7Kq"}},266:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(0),o=n.n(a),r=n(55),i=n.n(r),s=n(27),c=n(29),l=(n(42),{isOpen:!1}),p=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:l;switch((arguments.length>1?arguments[1]:void 0).type){case"OPEN SIDE DRAWER":return{isOpen:!0};case"CLOSE SIDE DRAWER":return{isOpen:!1}}return e},h=n(10),u=n(11),d=n(13),m=n(12),_=n(14),w=n(9),b=n(15),g=n(28),E=n.n(g),f=n(19),v=n.n(f),y=function(){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:v.a.body},o.a.createElement("img",{src:E.a,alt:"logo",className:v.a.logo}),o.a.createElement("div",{className:v.a.Body},o.a.createElement("p",null,"Welcome to the quiz website for the ECX Front End Track.",o.a.createElement("br",null),"This is just a way to revise what you have learnt so far.")),o.a.createElement("div",{className:v.a.base},o.a.createElement("div",{className:v.a.tests},o.a.createElement(w.b,{to:"/week-one",exact:!0},"Week 1"),o.a.createElement("br",null),o.a.createElement(w.b,{to:"/week-two",exact:!0},"Week 2"),o.a.createElement(w.b,{to:"/week-three",exact:!0},"Week 3"))),o.a.createElement("footer",null,"Built by Irene and Akin"))},O=[{question:"Which of these is not necessary for front-end web development?",option:["Web Browser","Code Editor","A Computer","Anaconda"],answerIndex:3},{question:"What department is tasked with turning a UI design into code?",option:["UI/UX","Front-End","Dev-Ops","Back-End"],answerIndex:1},{question:"Which of these is the odd one out?",option:["PHP","HTML","JavaScript","CSS"],answerIndex:0},{question:"Which of these is responsible for adding styles to a webpage?",option:["GO","Python","CSS","JavaScript"],answerIndex:2},{question:"The programming language of the web is?",option:["Go","Python","Ruby","Java Script"],answerIndex:3}],k=[{question:"What is the full meaning of HTML?",option:["HYPER TEXT MARKED LANGUAGE","HYPER TEXT MARKUP LANGUAGE","HIGH TEXT MARKED LANGUAGE","HIGH TEXT MARKUP LANGUAGE"],answerIndex:1},{question:"Which one of these represents the head of a HTML document",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:["<h1></h1>","<html></html>","<head></head>","<header></header>"],answerIndex:2},{question:"Which of these is the correct way to write HTML attributes?",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:['<h1 style"=color:red;"></h1>','<h1 style="color:red;"></h1>','<h1 style:"color"="red;"></h1>',"<h1 style:\"color:'red';\"></h1>"],answerIndex:1},{question:"Which of these is the odd one out",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:["<h7></h7>","<h6></h6>","<h8></h8>","<h></h>"],answerIndex:1},{question:"Where is the page tite that shows in the browser tab defined?",option:["In the head tag","In the body tag","Right above the Document type","In the footer"],answerIndex:0},{question:"How do you define a paragraph in HTML?",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:["<paragraph></paragraph>","<q></q>","<p></p>","<p><p/>"],answerIndex:2},{question:"Which of these is the correct way to write multiple HTML attributes?",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:['<h1 style"=color:red; font-size: 40px;"></h1>','<h1 style="color:red; font-size: 40px"></h1>','<h1 style:"color"="red"; "font-size"="40px"></h1>',"<h1 style:\"color:'red'; font-size:'40px'\"></h1>"],answerIndex:1},{question:"Which of these is the correct way to make a superscript?",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:["<super></super>",'<p style="super"></p>',"<h1 style:super></h1>","<sup></sup>"],answerIndex:3}],x=[{question:'How would you add a quote " " to a text?',type:"snippet",language:"html",option:["<blockquote>I am a quote</blockquote",'<p style="quote">I am a quote</p>',"<q>I am a quote</q>","<quote></quote>"],answerIndex:2},{question:"what is placed in the cite attribute in a blockquote?",option:["The person who said it","Nothing","cite isn't used in blockquote","A link to the original quote"],answerIndex:3},{question:"Which of these is the correct way to write an abbreviation?",type:"snippet",language:"html",option:['<abbreviation title="World Health Organisation">WHO</abbreviation>','<abbr title="World Health Organisation">WHO</abbr>','<abb title="World Health Organisation">WHO</abb>','<abbreviation name="World Health Organisation">WHO</abbreviation>'],answerIndex:1},{question:"Why is it important to comment your code?",option:["To make your code more understandable","To make your code run faster","To make your code cleaner","To speed up code execution"],answerIndex:0},{question:"What is the maximum value any of the colors can have in rgb(10, 20, 30)",option:["100","225","125","255"],answerIndex:3},{question:'What does the "a" in "rgba" define?',option:["border","hue","opacity","light intensity"],answerIndex:2},{question:"Which of these is the correct way to make a red heading with a border round it?",type:"snippet",language:"css",option:["h1 {color: red;\nborder: 1px solid}","h1 {color: red;\nborder: solid red}","h1 {color: red;\nborder-right: solid red}"],answerIndex:0}],q=n(30),I=n.n(q),S=function(e){function t(){var e,n;Object(h.a)(this,t);for(var a=arguments.length,o=new Array(a),r=0;r<a;r++)o[r]=arguments[r];return(n=Object(d.a)(this,(e=Object(m.a)(t)).call.apply(e,[this].concat(o)))).state={isOpen:!1},n.toggleSide=function(){var e=n.state.isOpen,t=n.props,a=t.open,o=t.close;e?(o(),n.setState({isOpen:!1})):(a(),n.setState({isOpen:!0}))},n}return Object(_.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:I.a.header,id:"head"},o.a.createElement("img",{src:E.a,alt:"logo",className:I.a.Logo}),o.a.createElement("div",{className:I.a.hamBurger,onClick:this.toggleSide,onKeyPress:this.toggleSide,tabIndex:0,role:"button"},o.a.createElement("div",null),o.a.createElement("div",null),o.a.createElement("div",null)))}}]),t}(a.Component),N=n(16),W=n.n(N),C=function(e){var t=e.isOpen,n=e.close,a=e.permanent,r=void 0!==a&&a;return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"".concat(W.a.SideDrawer," ").concat(t?W.a.open:W.a.close," ").concat(r?W.a.permanent:"")},o.a.createElement("ul",null,X.map(function(e){var t=e.pathname,a=e.hash,r=e.name;return o.a.createElement("li",{key:r},o.a.createElement(w.b,{to:{pathname:t,hash:a},className:"home"===r?W.a.home:W.a.navLink,onClick:n,exact:!0},r))})))},H=n(20),A=n.n(H),T=n(270),j=n(269),D=n(2),L=n.n(D),R=function(e){function t(){var e;return Object(h.a)(this,t),(e=Object(d.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).call(this))).selected=function(t,n){t!==n?e.setState({circleClass:"".concat(L.a.circle," ").concat(L.a.slim),innerClass:"".concat(L.a.inner," ").concat(L.a.incInner),containerCLass:"".concat(L.a.container," ").concat(L.a.false),snippetClass:"".concat(L.a.containerSnippet," ").concat(L.a.false)}):e.setState({circleClass:"".concat(L.a.circle," ").concat(L.a.slim),innerClass:"".concat(L.a.inner," ").concat(L.a.incInner),containerCLass:"".concat(L.a.container," ").concat(L.a.true),snippetClass:"".concat(L.a.containerSnippet," ").concat(L.a.true)})},e.state={circleClass:L.a.circle,innerClass:L.a.inner,containerCLass:L.a.container,snippetClass:L.a.containerSnippet},e}return Object(_.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this,t=this.state,n=t.circleClass,a=t.innerClass,r=t.containerCLass,i=t.snippetClass,s=this.props,c=s.option,l=s.type,p=void 0===l?"text":l,h=s.answer,u=s.language;return o.a.createElement("div",null,"text"===p?o.a.createElement("div",{className:r},o.a.createElement("div",{className:n},o.a.createElement("div",{className:a})),o.a.createElement("div",{className:L.a.option,onClick:this.selected.bind(this,c,h),onKeyPress:this.selected,role:"button",tabIndex:0},c)):"snippet"===p?o.a.createElement(T.a,{className:i,language:u,showLineNumbers:!0,style:j.a,onClick:function(){return e.selected(c,h)}},c):"")}}]),t}(a.Component),G=function(e){return e.children},B=function(e){var t=e.questions;return o.a.createElement("div",{className:A.a.container,id:"test"},o.a.createElement(G,null,o.a.createElement(C,{isOpen:!0,permanent:!0}),o.a.createElement("div",{className:A.a.rightSide},t.map(function(e,t){var n=e.type,a=e.option,r=e.question,i=e.answerIndex,s=e.language;return o.a.createElement(G,{key:a},o.a.createElement("h1",{className:A.a.question,key:a},"".concat(t+1,") "),r),o.a.createElement("div",{className:A.a.options},a.map(function(e){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:A.a.option,key:e},o.a.createElement(R,{option:e,type:n,key:e,answer:a[i],language:s}))})))}))))},M=function(e){function t(e){var n;Object(h.a)(this,t);var a=(n=Object(d.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).call(this,e))).props.isOpen;return n.state={isOpen:a},n}return Object(_.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this.props,t=e.openNav,n=e.closeNav,a=e.isOpen,r=e.week;return o.a.createElement(G,null,o.a.createElement(S,{open:t,close:n}),o.a.createElement(C,{isOpen:a,close:n}),o.a.createElement(B,{questions:r}))}}]),t}(a.Component),P=Object(c.b)(function(e){return{isOpen:e.isOpen}},function(e){return{openNav:function(){return e({type:"OPEN SIDE DRAWER"})},closeNav:function(){return e({type:"CLOSE SIDE DRAWER"})}}})(M),z=function(){return o.a.createElement(P,{week:O})},U=function(){return o.a.createElement(P,{week:k})},Q=function(){return o.a.createElement(P,{week:x})},J=n(61),K=n.n(J),X=[{pathname:"/",name:"home"},{pathname:"/week-one",hash:"#test",name:"week one"},{pathname:"/week-two",hash:"#test",name:"week two"},{pathname:"/week-three",hash:"#test",name:"week three"}],F=function(){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:K.a.General},o.a.createElement(b.a,{path:"/",exact:!0,component:y}),o.a.createElement(b.a,{path:"/week-one",component:z}),o.a.createElement(b.a,{path:"/week-two",component:U}),o.a.createElement(b.a,{path:"/week-three",component:Q}))},Y=function(e){function t(){return Object(h.a)(this,t),Object(d.a)(this,Object(m.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(_.a)(t,e),Object(u.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){return o.a.createElement(w.a,{basename:"/AkinAguda/ecx-frontEnd-site"},o.a.createElement("div",null,o.a.createElement(F,null)))}}]),t}(a.Component);Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));var Z=Object(s.b)(p);i.a.render(o.a.createElement(c.a,{store:Z},o.a.createElement(Y,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(function(e){e.unregister()})},28:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n.p+"static/media/brand.50e047d0.svg"},30:function(e,t,n){e.exports={header:"Nav_header__2i12B",Logo:"Nav_Logo__y7BAs",hamBurger:"Nav_hamBurger__1z6yJ",stretch1:"Nav_stretch1__2iMXz",stretch2:"Nav_stretch2__1rQko",stretch3:"Nav_stretch3__o1UiA"}},42:function(e,t,n){},61:function(e,t,n){e.exports={General:"routes_General__24boz"}},62:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(266)}},[[62,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.fe17fe9e.chunk.js.map